Guide to the James and Margaret Goff Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Document Service, Series I
  - Document Service publications
    - Jose Miguez-Bonino: "The Political Attitude of Protestants in Latin America", 1973 Nov 25 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - "Message to the Panamanian People, Easter, 1973, from the Methodist Church of Panama", 1974 March 10 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - "Message from Christian Communicators in Latin America: The Chaclacayo (Peru) Document of August, 1973", 1974 May 5 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Gustavo Gutierrez: "Praxis of Liberation and the Christian Faith", 1974 Aug 15 (Box 45, Folder 818)
    - Enrique Lomas Arellano: "The Gospel: Opium or Message of Liberation?", 1976 April (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Jose L. Casals: "Hymns of Commitment: Ethical and Theological Values"; "Salvador Allende" - words and music by Lois Kroehler; article from National Reporter, 1976 Juloy (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Pablo Richard: "The Search for God in the Political Struggle of Liberation", 1976 August (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - "The Church in the Third World: Statement of the Ecumenical Dialogue of Third World Theologians at Dar-es-Salaam, Tanzania, August 5-12, 1976", 1977 February (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Alfonso Castillo, S.J.: "Medellin: Political Rupture, Christian Advance", 1978 December (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Three documents, including "Theology and the Liberation of Man" by Ruben A. Alves, 1977 March (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - "Five Years of Christians for Socialism", 1978 January (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Jose Miguez Bonino: "Popular Piety in Latin America", 1978 February (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Gustavo Gutierrez: "The Poor in the Church", 1978 March (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Joseph Comblin: "The Latin American Church Since Vatican II", 1978 June (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Luis N. Rivera: "The Mission of the Church and the Development of a Caribbean Theology of Liberation", 1978 July (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - "Out of Hunger into the Fight" by the ONIS Priest Movement, 1978 August (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Augusto Cotto: "We Need Dialogue Between Cuba and the Rest of the Continent", 1978 September (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Pablo Richard: "The Latin American Church Between Fear and Hope" (1959-1978)", 1978 Apr (Box 45, Folder 818)
    - Gustavo Gutierrez:"The Power of the Poor in History", 1979 January (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - "The Essence of Religion: to Impugn the System - an interview with Enrique Dussel" by Enrique Maza, 1978 Oct (Box 45, Folder 818)
    - "Americans, Look Seriously at What your Government is Doing in Nicaragua" by Professors of the Baptist Seminary, Mexico City, 1978 Nov (Box 45, Folder 818)
    - Materials re. Honduras, 1981 Aug (Box 45, Folder 819)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent January 1982, incl. Interview with Archbishop of Managua by Manuel Eugarrios; Protest letter to the New York Times from the Presbyterian Church re. Nicaraguan government; Interview with Leonardo Boff by Teofilo Cabestrero; Message from Ecumenical Eje of Nicaragua, 1982 Jan 15 (Box 45, Folder 819)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent February - March 1982, incl. CEPRES statement (Protestant Commission for the Promotion of Social Responsibility); Message of Catholic Episcopal Conference of Nicaragua; Nicaraguan Government Communique on the Message; Statement of Committee of U.S. Citizens Living in Nicaragua, 1982 Feb 20 (Box 45, Folder 820)
    - Material sent March - April 1982, incl. John F. Wilson: "The Situation on the Atlantic Coast of Nicaragua"; "Open Letter to the People and Congress of the United States" by the Association of Nicaraguan Clergy (ACLEN); "We're Taking Up Arms to Defend Life": Reflection of Basic Ecclesial Communities in Managua concerning military intervention; Pastoral Letter from CEPAD to the Christian Churches and People of the United States and to All People of Good Will; "Jesuit Social Scientists Condemn U.S. Intervention", 1982 Mar 24 (Box 45, Folder 821)
    - Statements of Nicaraguan Christians in support of Nicaraguan Government; Material sent March - April 1982, incl. John F. Wilson: "The Situation on the Atlantic Coast of Nicaragua"; "Open Letter to the People and Congress of the United States" by the Association of Nicaraguan Clergy (ACLEN); "We're Taking Up Arms to Defend Life": Reflection of Basic Ecclesial Communities in Managua concerning military intervention; Pastoral Letter from CEPAD to the Christian Churches and People of the United States and to All People of Good Will; "Jesuit Social Scientists Condemn U.S. Intervention", 1982 Apr 15 (Box 45, Folder 821)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent May - July 1982, incl."Christians in Nicaragua's Sandinista Revolution": official communique from the National Directorate of the FSLN; "An Open Letter to the Churches of Western Europe and North American That Have Shown Solidarity With Us": Christian Peace Conference in Latin America; "Manipulation of the Catastrophe" by the UCR (Revolutionary Christian University Students); Material sent August 1982, incl. Interview with Leonardo Boff by Teofilo Cabestrero; "Protestants Salute the Nicaraguan Revolution on its Third Anniversary": ANPEN (Associacion Nacional de Pastores Evangelicos de Nicaragua); "To the Nicaraguan People and Our Brothers and Sisters Abroad": Baptist Convention of Nicaragua; "Christians and the Revolution, Part I: The Catholic Church in the Three Years of the Revolution" by Teofilo Cabestrero, 1982 May (Box 45, Folder 822)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent August 1982, incl. "Our Revolutionary Culture is a Culture of Peace, Conviviality and Forgiveness": address by Fr. Ernesto Cardenal, Nicaraguan Minister of Culture; "Nicaragua Rejects $5.1 Million from AID, a communique from Nicaragua's International Fund for Reconstruction"; "Pronouncement by Students of the Protestant Faculty of Theological Studies", 1982 Aug (Box 45, Folder 823)
    - Papers re. tensions between Sandinist Government and Catholic Church in Nicaragua; Material sent September - December 1982, incl. "There is Conflict, Not Persecution" by Jose Arguello; "The FSLN National Directorate calls for calmness and prudence..."; "Unity Must Be Grounded in Christ - a reflection on the Pope's letter of June 29, 1982" by Jose Arguello; "Protestant Pastors in Dialogue with the Government" by Miguel Angel Casco; "A Communique of the Nicaraguan Government Junta Concerning the Meeting of Foreign Ministers Held in San Jose, Costa Rica"; "A Letter from Com. Tomas Borge, Nicaraguan Minister of the Interior ...."; "Stop the Genocidal Bands...": a letter from Christian communities of Northern Nicaragua; "A Message of Love and Peace to Honduran Christians..."; "Christians and the Revolution, Part II" by Miguel Angel Casco; "An Alert to the Protestant Churches of Nicaragua" by CEPRES; "Nicaragua's Consecration to the Immaculate Heart of Mary" by Jose Arguello, 1982 Sep-Dec (Box 45, Folder 824)
    - Papers re. tensions between Sandinist Government and Catholic Church in Nicaragua; Material sent March 1983, incl. Excerpts from Pope's speeches in Nicaragua; Welcoming speech of Com. Daniel Ortega Saavedra; A Christian Reflection on the Pope's Visit; Farewell speech of Com. Daniel Ortega Saavedra; "Instead of peace, he left confusion" by Guillermo Thorndike; "A Letter from Manugua to the Pilgrim for Peace, John Paul II" by Maria Lopez Vigil; FSLN communique, 1983 Mar (Box 45, Folder 825)
    - Materials re. Nicaraguan Popular Revolution; Material sent July 1983, incl. "Letter of Support for the Church of the Poor in Nicaragua"; "Response to Address by President Reagan to Joint Session of Congress by U.S. Religious Personnel in Nicaragua"; "Letter to Christian Women in the United States"; "A Summons by the FSLN to Defend the Fatherland Against Reagan's Undeclared War", 1983 Jul 19 (Box 45, Folder 826)
    - Materials re. reaction of Catholic Church to law of obligatory military service in Nicaragua: Material sent September 1983, incl. "General Considerations on Military Service"; "Christian Groups Respond to the Nicaraguan Bishops Communique on Military Service", 1983 Sep (Box 45, Folder 827)
    - Materials re. Reagan administration's aggression towards Nicaragua; Material sent October 1983, incl. "The National Situation in Nicaragua" - a report by World Council of Churches visitation team; "Peace Vigil in Jalapa," an account of a visit by an Ecumenical group of 150 persons from the U.S.; a statement on Nicaragua by religious of the Dominican Order; Letter to Nicaraguan Baptist Churches; Message from ANPEN, 1983 Oct (Box 45, Folder 828)
    - Materials re. Christian support for Sandinist Government:Material sent November 1983, incl. interview with Methodist Bishop Federico Pagura, President of the Latin America Council of Churches; "Dominicans Call for Solidarity with Nicaragua"; "Statement of Nicaraguan Catholics and Protestants on the Invasion of Grenada", "A Pentecostal Congregation Denounces U.S. Aggression Against Nicaragua and Grenada", 1983 Nov (Box 45, Folder 829)
    - Materials re.Nicaragua, 1984 Jan (Box 45, Folder 830)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua:Material sent March 1984, incl. "What Moral Authority Have the Nicaraguan Bishops Earned in the Field of Politics," by Jose Manuel Ruiz; "The Challenge of Evangelism in a Revolutionary Society," by CEPRES, 1984 Mar (Box 45, Folder 831)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent April 1984, incl. message from the Government Junta of National Reconstruction; "Pastoral Letter from CEPRES..."; "Christians Speak About the Electoral Process", 1984 Apr 1 (Box 45, Folder 832)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent May 1984, incl. radio homily of Father Uriel Molina; Baptist Convention's pastoral letter; pronouncement of Ecumenical Committee of U. S. Church Personnel in Nicaragua, written by Richard Shaull; statement of Government Junta, 1984 May 1 (Box 45, Folder 833)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent June 1984, incl. re. Nicaraguan Catholic Bishops' Conference statement, 1984 Jun (Box 45, Folder 834)
    - Material sent July 1984, incl. "Is There Religious Persecution in Nicaragua?", by Mauro Jacomelli; "Catholic Schools in the Revolution"; Communique from Basic Christian Communities; Message from Eje Ecumenico, 1984 Jul (Box 45, Folder 835)
    - Material sent August - October 1984, incl. statements by Christian groups in honor of fifth anniversary of Sandinista victory; Resolution by Episcopal Church of Nicaragua; Message from Franciscan Friars of Nicaragua; Report of the Justice and Peace Commission of the Spanish Dominican Order of Men and Women Religious, 1984 Aug (Box 45, Folder 836)
    - Material sent November - December 1984, incl. statements of Nicaraguan Christian groups condemning U.S. aggression; "The Crisis of Nicaraguan Catholicism," by Francois Houtart, 1984 Nov-Dec (Box 45, Folder 837)
    - C.U.S.C.L.I.N: "Their Vote Decided: the 1984 Nicaraguan Elections - a report by the Committee of U.S. Citizens Living in Nicaragua", 1985 Jan (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent March - May 1985, incl. open letter to the U.S. Congress from 88 religious workers in Nicaragua; "Vision of God in the Poetry of Ernesto Cardenal," by Jose Arguello; testimonies of Christians in the war zones of Nicaragua; Latin American Council of Churches statement, 1985 Mar-May (Box 45, Folder 838)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent July - August 1985, incl. re. fast for peace of Nicaraguan Foreign Minister, Father Miguel d"Escoto; "United States Note to Nicaragua", 1985 Jul-Aug (Box 45, Folder 839)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent September 1985, incl. statement of Antonio Valdivieso Ecumenical Center in reply to accusations by some Catholic bishops that the center is working Against the hierarchy and seeking to divide the Church; statement by U.S. Presbyterian church personnel in Nicaragua, 1985 Sep (Box 45, Folder 840)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent October - December 1985, incl. observations of visitors from Brazil, Friar Leonardo Boff and Bishop Pedro Casaldaliga; "The Church in Nicaragua 20 Years After the Council," by Alejandro Von Rechnitz, S. J.; open letters to President Reagan, 1985 Oct-Dec (Box 45, Folder 841)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent January - March 1986, incl. message from Christians and religious leaders in Nicaragua to U.S. Congress, U.S. Catholic Conference, and NCCCUSA; Statement addressed to Cardinal Obando y Bravo; material re. Father Miguel d'Escoto; interview re. liberation theology with Pablo Richard; Statements of Nicaraguan Christians against funding of contras by U.S., 1986 Jan-Mar (Box 45, Folder 842)
    - Materials re. Nicaragua: Material sent April - August 1986, incl. articles re. Church-State relations in Nicaragua; re. Catholic Bishop Pablo Antonio Vega, who sided with Reagan Administration, 1986 Apr-Aug (Box 45, Folder 843)
    - Materials re. Central America, 1988 -1990 (Box 2, Folder 40-42)
    - Undated papers and cover letters with no documents attached, 1971-1972, no date (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Related material and correspondence
    - Raul Macin (Drafts/Correspondence), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Ruben A. Alves (Drafts/Correspondence), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Koster Reports (Unedited), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous Documents (No Issue Date) (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence with Subscribers, 1969 Dec-1973 (Box 2, Folder 48-53)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Writings and Translations, Series II
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes the following subseries: a) Writings by the Goffs: filed together with supporting materials, first according to author, then chronologically, with incomplete projects following; b) Writings by others, divided into unpublished and published, then filed alphabetically by author; c) Occasional translations by the Goffs; d) Other publications of the Goffs; e) Publications of other document services.
  - Writings by the Goffs
    - By James Goff
      - "What's Behind the Persecution in Colombia?", 1961 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - "How the Roman Catholic Church Controls Public Schools in Colombia", 1962 (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
      - "U.S. Aid to Colombia's Schools", 1964 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Dissertation Abstract, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - "Junto a La Cruz de Jesus", 1967 Mar 24 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - "La Situación Actual de Las Instituciones Educativas Presbiterianas", 1967 Jun 26 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - "Survey Report-Colombia", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Book Review of Camilo Torres, 1970 Dec 10 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Reaction to Tom Sanders' Article, 1970 Summer (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Development-the Latin American View, 1970 Oct (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - A New Form of Missionary Power, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - "Can a US Missionary Serve in Latin America?", 1971 (Box 46a, Folder 845)
      - Observations about the Article "A Lesson in World-Winning", 1971 Nov 29 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Human Liberation-the Heart of Mission, 1972 Mar (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Interview with James N. Wright, 1987 Sep 4 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Protestantism in Latin America/Preaching in Global Context, 1987/n.d. (1980s?) (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - "The Prostitution of the Iowa", 1986 (Box 46a, Folder 846)
      - "Protestantism in Latin America" in Church and Society, Nov/Dec 1986-Jan/Feb 1987 (Box 46a, Folder 847)
      - "The Miranda Statements and their Significance", 1987 (Box 46a, Folder 848)
      - "Hostage Conned", 1987 (Box 46a, Folder 849)
      - "Some Thoughts about Gerald H. Anderson's 'American Protestants in Pursuit of Mission: 1886-1986", 1988 (Box 46a, Folder 850)
      - "Who will Liberate us from the Cold Warriors?", 1988 (Box 46a, Folder 851)
      - "The Maligning of the Valdivieso Ecumenical Center", 1989 (Box 46a, Folder 852)
      - "A Christian Institution is Maligned", 1989 (Box 46a, Folder 853)
      - "How I Saw the Nicaraguan Elections", 1990 (Box 46a, Folder 854)
      - "Keeping a Watch on the Elections in Nicaragua", 1990 (Box 46a, Folder 855)
      - Re: Nicaragua Election, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - Some observations about "Impacto Presbiteriano", ca. 1990 (Box 48, Folder 891)
      - Re: Quincentenary of Columbus, 1991-92 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - Quincentenary of Columbus (Drafts) (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - Re: Rigoberta Menchu, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Presbyterian Missionaries in Nicaragua, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 892)
      - "Another Look at El Salvador", 1991 (Box 46a, Folder 856)
      - "USA has harassed Cuba" in The Presbyterian Outlook, 1992 (Box 46a, Folder 857)
      - "No Indians need Apply", 1992 (Box 46a, Folder 858)
      - "A Challenge to the Churches", 1992 (Box 46a, Folder 859)
      - "Pastors Challenge Embargo" in The Presbyterian Outlook, 1993 (Box 46a, Folder 860)
      - "An Example of Patriotism" in The Presbyterian Outlook, 1993 (Box 46a, Folder 861)
      - "Source of Confusion - The White House or Church Personnel in Central America" in The Presbyterian Outlook, 1993 (Box 46a, Folder 862)
      - "Cuba Policy: A Challenge to the Churches", 1993 (Box 46a, Folder 863)
      - "Alien Dilemma", 1993 (Box 46a, Folder 864)
      - "Asian Women Doing Theology" (Box 46a, Folder 865)
      - "A Church in Crisis" (Box 46a, Folder 866)
      - "Presbyterian Missionaries in Nicaragua" (Box 46a, Folder 867)
      - "Standing with Exiles" (Box 46a, Folder 868)
      - "Theology in the Rebellion" (Box 46a, Folder 869)
      - "When we protested Arms" (Box 46a, Folder 870)
      - "Toward a more informed involvement in mission" (Box 46a, Folder 871)
      - "Why can't we travel to Cuba?" (Box 46a, Folder 872)
      - Writings of Goff (Recorded) (Box 46a, Folder 873)
      - "When the Spirit Moves" (Box 46a, Folder 875)
      - "Church and Liberation" (Box 46a, Folder 876)
      - "The Unpleasant side of Pleasantville" (Box 46a, Folder 877)
      - "Colombian Priests call for immediate Changes in Society" (Box 46a, Folder 878)
      - "Turmoil in the Roman Catholic Church of Colombia" (Box 46a, Folder 879)
    - By Margaret Goff
      - A Child Shall Lead Them, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - The Protestant Church in Colombia, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - Education in Colombia, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Nicaragua, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - By JEG and MPG
      - Various, 1967, 1972, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - Miscellaneous writings or translations, 1987, 1992, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 893)
    - Incomplete Writing Projects
      - "The Question of Divorce", n.d. (1960s?) (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Sunday School Times, 1966-67 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - H. Money Rebuttal (Original Articles), 1967-68 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - H. Money Rebuttal (Background Material), 1965-68 (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - H. Money Rebuttal (Correspondence), 1966-68 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - "The Religious Situation", 1968-70 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - Wall Street Journal Response, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Writings of Others
    - Unpublished
      - A-Ca (Box 4, Folder 87-91)
      - Carillo (W.C.C.) (Box 4, Folder 92)
      - Castillo (Box 4, Folder 93)
      - Ce-Cy (Box 4, Folder 94-95)
      - Costas (Box 4, Folder 96)
      - D (Box 4, Folder 97-98)
      - Epps, Fals-Borda (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - Fe-H (Box 5, Folder 100-102)
      - Illich (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - J-L (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Lara-Brand (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - M-P (Box 5, Folder 106-110)
      - R-V (Box 6, Folder 111-114)
      - Vallier (Box 6, Folder 115-116)
      - W-Z (Box 6, Folder 117)
      - Wheaton (Box 6, Folder 118)
      - Anonymous (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Published
      - A-H (Box 6, Folder 120-123)
      - Illich (Box 7, Folder 124)
      - J-L (Box 7, Folder 125)
      - Kerr (Box 7, Folder 126)
      - M-S (Box 7, Folder 127-128)
      - T-Z (Box 7a, Folder 129)
  - Translations
    - El Tiempo, 1964 Ot 26 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Rene Garcia (T. M.P.G), 1970 Jul 4 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Tercer Mundo Sacerdotes (Draft, Partial), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Alves (T. J.E.G. and Harriet Goff Guerrero), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Alves-Background, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - J. and E. Wright, (T. Harriet Goff Guerrero, Francisco Guerrero, Fred and Charles Goff), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Aguilar, "Who Gets Imprisoned in Bolivia?" (draft translation), William Morales B., "Bishop Romero in the Neoliberal Context", Francois Houtart, "Camilo Torres, Prophet and Social Warrior: His Meaning for our Time", 1972 Aug 21 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Report on Colombia-UPCUSA, J.E.G., and M.P.G., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Julio de Santa Ana (incomplete draft), n.d. (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-88 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Press releases/Newsletters
    - Miscellaneous
      - Publications, press releases, and newsletters, 1953-66, 68, 96, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - CEDEC Bulletins
      - Bulletins (1-39), 1952 Feb 15-1957 May 7 (Box 8, Folder 141-142)
      - Bulletins (41-81), Supplement, 1957 Aug 31-1963 Sep 30 (Box 8, Folder 143-145)
    - "Friendship Findings"
      - Newsletter (1-26), 1990 Jul 1-1995 Oct (Box 8, Folder 146)
      - Article Drafts, 1990-94 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Other Documentation Services
    - CENDOC (Centro de Documentación en Comunicación Educativa), 1972 Jul 25 (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - CIDOC (69/163-72/384) (Box 9, Folder 150-154)
    - CIP Documenta, 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - Cuba Resource Center (Background), 1971-73 (Box 9, Folder 156)
    - Cuba Resource Center Newsletters (Vol. 1, No. 1-3), 1971 Feb-Jun (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - Cuba Resource Center Newsletters (Vol. 2, No. 1-3), 1972 Jan-May (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - Cuba Resource Center Newsletters (Vol. 2, No. 4-6/Vol. 3, No. 1), 1972 Jul-1973 Apr (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Documentation for Action Groups in Asia (DAGA), 1972-73 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Ecumenical Pres Service (EPS), 1990-91 (Box 9, Folder 161)
    - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA), ATW 4-13 (A.T. Weil), 1972 Mar-Dec (Box 10, Folder 162)
    - ICWA, FJM 11-26 (F.J. McDonald), 1969 May-1971 Mar (Box 10, Folder 163)
    - ICWA, FJM 31-40 (F.J. McDonald) "Report From a Cuban Prison", 1972 Sep-1973 Jul (Box 10, Folder 164)
    - ICWA, FJM 41-48 (F.J. McDonald) "Report From a Cuban Prison", 1973 Jul-Aug (Box 10, Folder 165)
    - ICWA, FMF 44-52 (F.M. Foland), 1972 Feb-1973 Feb (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - ICWA, TGS 4, 14 (T.G. Sanders), 1967 Sep, 1988 Aug (Box 10, Folder 167)
    - ISAL (Iglesia y Sociedad en América Latina) Introductory Materials, 1967-70 (Box 10, Folder 168)
    - ISAL Misc., 1966-71 (Box 10, Folder 169)
    - ISAL Booklets, Poster, 1962-69 (Box 10, Folder 170)
    - ISAL Asamblea Bolivia, 1969 Aug (Box 10, Folder 171)
    - ISAL Consulta, Piriapolis, Uruguay, 1967 Dec (Box 10, Folder 172)
    - ISAL Boletín, 1961-64 (Box 10, Folder 173)
    - ISAL Boletín de Accion Social, 1964-68 (Box 10, Folder 174)
    - ISAL Boletín Estudios, No. 2-4, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 175)
    - ISAL Carta Latinoamericana, No. 3-10, 13-20, 1965-69 (Box 10, Folder 176)
    - ISAL Fichas de ISAL, ANO. 1, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 177)
    - ISAL Carta de ISAL, No. 1-4, 8, 1968-70 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - ISAL Fichas de ISAL, ANO. 3, No. 19-29, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 179)
    - ISAL Fichas de ISAL, ANO. 4, No. 30-41, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - ISAL Abstracts, Vol. 1, No. 4-10, 1968 Oct-1969 Apr (Box 11, Folder 181)
    - ISAL Misur, 1968, 1969, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 182)
    - ISAL Paso, No. 2-52, 1972 May-1973 May (Box 11, Folder 183-187)
    - ISAL Colombia Introductory Documents, 1967-69 (Box 11, Folder 188)
    - ISAL Colombia Boletín, 1969 Jan, 1970 Feb, May (Box 11, Folder 189)
    - ISAL Colombia Zona Norte Publicaciones, No. 6, 7, 13, 15, 18, 1969-70 (Box 11, Folder 190)